[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "What is the reaction of the Afghani people to this announcement by the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "To be honest, it's hard to tell.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "I mean aren't the Taliban just waiting in the mountains for the American troops to pull out and just to get back to what they did before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "You make a good point there, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Or hasn't it really been a counterterrorist operation that will now continue with more emphasis on Afghan troops than American troops?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Well, not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Have they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "No, they really haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "So isn't he entitled to remind the American people that it was a pretty successful mission, that it got rid of a pretty awful man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "But he didn't do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "What is the historical significance of the president's visit to Afghanistan tonight and the speech he's made outlining the future there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Well, I think it's very important.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bagram Air Base"]}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "No, he didn't get into, you know, a lot of politic -- political talk if you will in this 10-minute address he gave to the nation from the Bagram Air Base.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Let me turn to you, Doug Brinkley, I mean is that a fair criticism of the president, do you think, that he's just -- really this is just cheap politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "No, it's cheap politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Doug Brinkley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What was your reaction to that quote there from the Senate Armed Services Committee member?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNPS", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well, that was over the top.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate Armed Services Committee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Has America really got more out of this whole conflict in Afghanistan than the Soviets did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "That's yet to be determined.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "When you look at President Obama's foreign policies since he became president, are you impressed by the way that he has conducted it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "I am, I am personally impressed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "But isn't it just weird that in the modern political world with the rhetoric as it is that he can't even get credit for something so straightforward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Well, it's also a reminder in the great sweep of history that it's very hard to judge presidential decisions, presidential administrations at the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "He's got a fight on his hands, doesn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, he certainly has a fight on his hands.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Dr. Martin Luther King", "Civil Rights Movement", "CBS News"]}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "When you look back at it, when you finished the book and shut the page, which of all the stories was the one that had the most personal connection for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I would say covering Dr. Martin Luther King in the Civil Rights Movement, which was my first big assignment for CBS News.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Do you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I get angry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Will it ever properly recover from that day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "ATHER: Well, my personal opinion is we have not fully recovered.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq", "Afghanistan"]}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Do you think American responded the right way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "I don't in this regard -- again, my personal opinion -- I think the sort of taking the emphasis off Iraq after the initial success and placing it on Afghanistan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "When you look back on the whole thing, knowing everything you now know, is there anything you would have done differently, with the great benefit of hindsight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Well, we don't have the great benefit of hindsight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Do you believe to this day those documents were genuine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Have you ever had any conversation with President Bush since that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Once.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dwight Eisenhower"]}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Who was the one if you could choose one guy to lead your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Dwight Eisenhower would probably be my choice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "When you covered the Civil Rights Movement, did you ever imagine in your lifetime there would be a black president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Not only did I not imagine it, we used to sit around in the shank of the evening over an adult beverage talking about civil rights.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Civil Rights Movement"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "May I answer that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "That wasn't a question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Be that inquisitive, that interrogatory?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Frankly, I don't think any reporter could do it today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "When you take an overview, what do you think of modern journalism standards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Well, American journalism is in crisis, in my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]